<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<frapi-config>
 <actions>
  <action>
   <name>Collection</name>
   <enabled>1</enabled>
   <public>1</public>
   <description>This is an example of a collection. A collection is a bucket of resources. In this case, you can only POST and DELETE this collection.&#13;
&#13;
POST: A post will add a new resource to a collection. You have to pass a &quot;name&quot; parameter.&#13;
&#13;
DELETE: Delete collection will remove the collection of resources from the system.&#13;
&#13;
Try it with &quot;curl -X POST http://api.frapi/collection -d '{&quot;name&quot;:&quot;new&quot;}' -H 'Content-Type: application/json'&#13;
&#13;
</description>
   <route>/collection</route>
   <hash>a0caa1c9f6c5ba636005b312918e7ce6acf70ccb</hash>
   <parameters>
    <parameter>
     <name>name</name>
     <required>0</required>
    </parameter>
   </parameters>
  </action>
  <action>
   <name>Resource</name>
   <enabled>1</enabled>
   <public>1</public>
   <description>This is the resource contained in a certain collection group. &#13;
&#13;
PUT: A put with the &quot;name&quot; parameter will update the name of the resource&#13;
&#13;
DELETE: Deletes the resource.&#13;
&#13;
GET: This retrieves the information relative to the resource contained in the collection</description>
   <route>/collection/:resource</route>
   <hash>3ecc1f98f5c2292d41150143083df87ea81dca08</hash>
   <parameters>
    <parameter>
     <name>name</name>
     <required>0</required>
    </parameter>
   </parameters>
  </action>
  <action>
   <name>Siblings</name>
   <enabled>1</enabled>
   <public>1</public>
   <description>This is a collection of sibling for a resource. This only accepts POST, DELETE, GET and HEAD. &#13;
&#13;
POST: A post will add a new sibling using the name parameter&#13;
&#13;
DELETE: This deletes the siblings connections, it removes all siblings in the collection&#13;
&#13;
GET: Retrieve a list of siblings and the relative information.&#13;
&#13;
HEAD: Fetch the meta information for the siblings.</description>
   <route>/collection/:resource/siblings</route>
   <hash>2f4d1cefc3bbb184dda9da882fac349558b8bb70</hash>
   <parameters>
    <parameter>
     <name>name</name>
     <required>0</required>
    </parameter>
   </parameters>
  </action>
  <action>
   <name>Sibling</name>
   <enabled>1</enabled>
   <public>1</public>
   <description>This is used to execute operations on a sibling resource. &#13;
&#13;
GET: Retrieve the information relative to a sibling&#13;
&#13;
DELETE: Remove a sibling for this resource&#13;
&#13;
HEAD: Retrieve the meta information relative to a sibling.&#13;
&#13;
</description>
   <route>/collection/:resource/siblings/:sibling</route>
   <hash>836d88aacf5906048737893dd4dc0469e353dc33</hash>
  </action>
 </actions>
</frapi-config>
